<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Antonio Lignan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Antonio Lignan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Antonio Lignan, All rights reserved - Opinions are my own</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 20:30:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Berlin</title>
      <link>/post/trip-to-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 20:30:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/trip-to-berlin/</guid>
      <description>Our trip to Berlin This is part of my previous Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends, which I&amp;rsquo;m trying to finish now in 2018.
After living and working abroad (in Berlin, Germany) for almost a year, having my family (finally) joining from Barcelona was both exciting and challenging. Packing and shipping all belongings and memories of 7 happy years over 1.800 kilometers is not an easy task. Needless to say, finding a flat in Berlin and dealing with the German bureaucracy on top of moving arrangements was particularly hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 2018 Challenge</title>
      <link>/projects/the-2018-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 16:00:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/the-2018-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The 2018 challenge This is a continuation from the 2017 challenge, a great one I hope to keep up for a very long time (and of course to finish).
This is a Meta project, as it will spawned several ones, thus I will not keep track of references here, but likely the related blog posts will include the Challenge 2018 tag.
And of course, I made a Github repository, in which I&amp;rsquo;m tracking the progress with the issues associated to my milestone completion:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Latest Geocaches</title>
      <link>/post/my-latest-geocaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 23:34:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-latest-geocaches/</guid>
      <description>My latest geocaches This is part of my Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends.
 Geocaching is a real-world, outdoor treasure hunting game using GPS-enabled devices. Participants navigate to a specific set of GPS coordinates and then attempt to find the geocache (container) hidden at that location.
 The history of Geocaching goes back to the year 2000 and the invention of GPS itself, with The Great American GPS Stash Hunt as a way to test the accuracy of the devices hunting a hidden bucket in Beavercreek, Oregon, near Portland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A book about Beers</title>
      <link>/post/a-book-about-beers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 21:05:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-book-about-beers/</guid>
      <description>A book about Beers (or how I am less ignorant) This is part of my Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends.
I bought The complete beer course a couple of months ago. It has traveled from my office and my flat in Berlin to my family house in Barcelona, however only until this week (few days before new year&amp;rsquo;s eve), I have finally found the time to began reading through its pages as part of my self-imposed challenge&amp;hellip; procrastination at its best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karaoke</title>
      <link>/post/karaoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 14:34:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/karaoke/</guid>
      <description>A Karaoke night This is part of my Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends.
Me, my wife and close friends went to the Almodobar&amp;rsquo;s karaoke bar in Barcelona - best night ever. We arrived at 23:30, which was great as the place was empty and we got the microphones to ourselves for almost an hour, enough to warm up and drink up (with the mandatory tequila/whiskey starter shot).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Daughter&#39;s Book</title>
      <link>/post/my-daughters-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 01:53:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-daughters-book/</guid>
      <description>My Daughter&amp;rsquo;s book This is part of my Challenge to make 26 years before 2017 ends.
I had an overdue and on-going task in my list: write a book for Erin, my daughter. I began writing a fantastic tale about Erin (our fearless heroin) and her surprising companion back in June 5th 2017, and now, November 25th it is finally done and sent to the printers.
Literally.

In Spanish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daughter&#39;s book with Pandoc (Spanish)</title>
      <link>/projects/childbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 20:57:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/childbook/</guid>
      <description>Erin&amp;rsquo;s children&amp;rsquo;s book This project is quite personal, as it is my first children&amp;rsquo;s story ever to be published solely for my daughter, Erin. It has a lot of inside jokes and references.
It was meant to be her birthday&amp;rsquo;s gift (last May), however due to work and other demons, it had to be postponed and now it will be her Christmas present - I hope I don&amp;rsquo;t screw up this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 2017 Challenge (Meta)</title>
      <link>/projects/the-2017-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 18:13:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/the-2017-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The 2017 challenge I was a bit bored and feeling depressed by end of September 2017 - living in Berlin eight months away from my family took most of my motivation and sanity, and I was getting my &amp;ldquo;kicks&amp;rdquo; only from my job, which is OK, but going also from developer to full manager has its downsides&amp;hellip;
At the Deadline Demo Party, while coding and watching some Intros, I made up my mind, and decided to challenge myself, and try to do 26 things before 2017 ended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making an Ajiaco</title>
      <link>/post/making-an-ajiaco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 22:38:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/making-an-ajiaco/</guid>
      <description>Making an Ajiaco This is part of my Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends.
The Ajiaco: one of the most traditional dishes of Colombia&amp;rsquo;s cuisine.

This dish is heavily served in Bogotá (the capital of Colombia), a thick hot soup (perfect for its cold days), made out of three types of potatoes, chicken, corn and the Galinsoga parviflora herb (called Guasca in Colombia).
There are tons of recipes on-line, but this type of dish has a strong root in families, thus I&amp;rsquo;m adapting the traditional recipe of my Auntie Cristina (hoping she won&amp;rsquo;t be highly disappointed at me afterwards).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Blog</title>
      <link>/projects/this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 23:49:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/this-blog/</guid>
      <description>This blog Creating an improving this blog is itself a project. Although I prefer to keep day to day progress in separate blog posts, I thought it would be good to keep track of the projects&amp;rsquo; evolution in a single placeholder - tags are also helpful and included, but this way I can have a better index for my own later reference.
Some specific about the blog, like minimum improvements like adding tags, categories, or internal links, are not necessarily tracked in a post, as I already made publicly available the blog&amp;rsquo;s sources - peep as you need!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Bonsai</title>
      <link>/post/my-new-bonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 22:47:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-new-bonsai/</guid>
      <description>My new bonsai This is part of my Challenge to make 26 things before 2017 ends.
Finally, after some consideration and procrastination, I decided to get a plant (and care for living beings). Fortunately, my current company has a great policy about office plants for employees.
Enter &amp;ldquo;Ligu&amp;rdquo; 
I got the bonsai from Exotenherz, an on-line shop specialized in plants, with an awesome shipping time and great care to transport plants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>